{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Swamp Cooler Installation Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40284/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40284,"taskName":"Swamp Cooler - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace a Swamp Cooler","xmTaskDescriptor":"Swamp Cooler Installation Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":238,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Airconditioning Swamp Cooler air airconditioners","textMessagingName":"Inst Swamp Cooler","rolloverLongDesc":"A kind of air conditioner that is primarily used in commercial applications \u0026 greenhouses.","rolloverShortDesc":"Rare in homes, also called evaporative cooler.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace a Swamp Cooler.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Swamp Cooler Installation - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install a Swamp Cooler","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":39,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Swamp Cooler Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Swamp Cooler - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Swamp Cooler Project","urlName":"Swamp-Cooler-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Swamp Cooler Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Costs, Reviews","searchKeywords":"Air conditioner, Swamp Cooler, cooling, hvac, AC, A/C, air, conditioner","emcCategoryOid":-12002,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":585,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40284/":{"taskOID":40284,"originalTaskOID":40284,"setID":585,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4766,"questionDisplayText":"Area to be Cooled","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of space will the swamp cooler cool?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5716,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Single Family Home","answerDisplayText":"Single Family Home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3882,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Mobile Home","answerDisplayText":"Mobile Home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2725,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garage, warehouse, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Garage, warehouse, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4767,"questionDisplayText":"Installation Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where do you want the swamp cooler installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5389,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Roof","answerDisplayText":"Roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6736,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall","answerDisplayText":"Wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6981,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Window","answerDisplayText":"Window","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":881,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Attic","answerDisplayText":"Attic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6937,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Rooms Needing Ductwork","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many rooms do you want the cooler connected to?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9591,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9592,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9593,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9594,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4","answerDisplayText":"4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9595,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"5","answerDisplayText":"5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9596,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"6","answerDisplayText":"6","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9597,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"7","answerDisplayText":"7","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9598,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"8","answerDisplayText":"8","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9599,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"9","answerDisplayText":"9","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9906,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"10 or more","answerDisplayText":"10 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4770,"questionDisplayText":"Control Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How will the swamp cooler be regulated?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4365,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"On/off switch","answerDisplayText":"On/off switch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6321,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Thermostat","answerDisplayText":"Thermostat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4766,"questionDisplayText":"Area to be Cooled","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of space will the swamp cooler cool?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5716,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Single Family Home","answerDisplayText":"Single Family Home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3882,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Mobile Home","answerDisplayText":"Mobile Home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2725,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garage, warehouse, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Garage, warehouse, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5716,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Single Family Home","answerDisplayText":"Single Family Home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3882,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Mobile Home","answerDisplayText":"Mobile Home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2725,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garage, warehouse, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Garage, warehouse, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4767,"questionDisplayText":"Installation Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where do you want the swamp cooler installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5389,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Roof","answerDisplayText":"Roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6736,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall","answerDisplayText":"Wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6981,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Window","answerDisplayText":"Window","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":881,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Attic","answerDisplayText":"Attic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5389,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Roof","answerDisplayText":"Roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6736,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall","answerDisplayText":"Wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6981,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Window","answerDisplayText":"Window","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":881,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Attic","answerDisplayText":"Attic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6937,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Rooms Needing Ductwork","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many rooms do you want the cooler connected to?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9591,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9592,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9593,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9594,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4","answerDisplayText":"4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9595,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"5","answerDisplayText":"5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9596,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"6","answerDisplayText":"6","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9597,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"7","answerDisplayText":"7","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9598,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"8","answerDisplayText":"8","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9599,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"9","answerDisplayText":"9","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9906,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"10 or more","answerDisplayText":"10 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9591,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9592,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9593,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9594,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4","answerDisplayText":"4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9595,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"5","answerDisplayText":"5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9596,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"6","answerDisplayText":"6","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9597,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"7","answerDisplayText":"7","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9598,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"8","answerDisplayText":"8","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9599,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"9","answerDisplayText":"9","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9906,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"10 or more","answerDisplayText":"10 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4770,"questionDisplayText":"Control Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How will the swamp cooler be regulated?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4365,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"On/off switch","answerDisplayText":"On/off switch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6321,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Thermostat","answerDisplayText":"Thermostat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4365,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"On/off switch","answerDisplayText":"On/off switch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6321,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Thermostat","answerDisplayText":"Thermostat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}